<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Free Software Camp</title>
    <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Free Software Camp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:23:05 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://camp.fsf.org.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:23:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camp.fsf.org.in/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Free Software Camp Privacy Policy v1.0 In Free Software camp we take individual privacy seriously, this document will act as the privacy policy for the Free Software Camp.
Data we collect from: Learner:  Personal Information: Name, Email, Gender and other communication details, Location. Technology Access Information: Internet access, computing device access. Priliminary Assessment Responses: Responses to the questions in the registration form that are to assess your exposure to free softwares and knowledge about Free Software philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/shed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:11:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camp.fsf.org.in/shed/</guid>
      <description>September 19-October 15 Mentors &amp; Learners Application Window People who wish to join the camp as mentor or learner can apply during this time.   October 17-October 24 Ice Breaking Learners get to know each other and know more about the program   October 25-November 3 Introduction to Free Software Get to know free software philosophy and install a GNU/Linux OS   November 4-November 11 Explore different areas of contribution Learn about different free software projects from contributors, and meet mentors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:25:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camp.fsf.org.in/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Free Software Camp Code of Conduct Free Software Camp, as part of the greater Free Software Community, assumes good faith on all those who wish to improve Free Software Projects. However, other experiences at other programs have shown us the need to adopt a Code of Conduct in which we state our expectations of all participants and organizers during the Free Software Camp.
This code of conduct applies to all participants of Free Software Camp, in addition to the FSCI Code of Conduct that applies to the FSCI community as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentors</title>
      <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/mentors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 12:46:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camp.fsf.org.in/mentors/</guid>
      <description>Mentor expectations  Free software contributions Identify projects in which they can mentor learners Commit 5 hours per week of mentoring during the 3 months of the mentorship - including answering questions, reviewing contributions, and meeting with learners Real-time meeting with learner(s) preferably once a week - either through real-time chat, video conference, or phone Timely review of contributions - if a mentor is unable to provide contribution review, they are responsible for finding community members who can Guidance to learners about how to work in a free software community Guidance to learners about time management Connect learners to the larger free software community Communicate with learners using Free Software tools</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camp.fsf.org.in/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://camp.fsf.org.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://camp.fsf.org.in/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>